Accessibility

Accessibility

Language

Language

### Electronic signature activation

How to activate NEW  
Certum's electronic signature?

### Electronic signature renewal

Renewal of Certum's e-signature  
step by step

Privacy Policy
--------------

OF THE INTERNET WEBSITE CERTUM.EU:
----------------------------------

[https://www.assecods.pl/wp-content/uploads/privacy\_policy\_ads.pdf](https://www.assecods.pl/wp-content/uploads/privacy_policy_ads.pdf)

This Privacy Policy sets forth the principles of collecting, processing and protecting personal data collected from Users during the use of the content and functionality of the Website.

### 1\. Definitions:

1) Asseco Data Systems S.A. – Asseco Data Systems S.A. seated in Gdańsk, at ul. Jana z Kolna 11, 80-864 Gdańsk, entered into the Register of Entrepreneurs of the National Court Register under KRS number 0000421310, kept by the District Court for Gdańsk-Północ in Gdańsk, VII Commercial Division of the National Court Register, NIP 517-035-94-58, REGON 180853177, whose share capital amounts to PLN 120,002,940.00 (fully paid up);  
2) CERTUM PCC – CERTUM Powszechne Centrum Certyfikacji Asseco Data Systems S.A., ul. Bajeczna 13, 71-838 Szczecin;  
3) Cookies – text files that are stored in the storage of the device used by the User while using the Website;  
4) President of UODO – President of the Office for Personal Data Protection with its registered office in Warsaw;  
5) Google Analytics – software that enables tracking traffic on the Website and monitoring marketing activities;  
6) Newsletter – electronic bulletin containing commercial information on products and services provided by Asseco Data Systems S.A.;  
7) Privacy Policy – this document setting forth the principles of collecting personal data, its processing, and protection by Asseco Data Systems S.A.;  
8) Website – websites or websites run by Asseco Data Systems  
S.A. listed in Appendix No. 1 to the Privacy Policy;  
9) GDPR Regulation – Regulation of the European Parliament and of the Council (EU) no. 2016/679 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)(Official EU Journal L no. 119 page 1);  
10) User – a natural person, a legal person or an organisational unit without legal personality;

### 2\. Data collected by the Website:

1) During your visit to the Website, the following information is automatically downloaded via Google Analytics or Cookies:  
a) IP address and domain name,  
b) the type of Internet browser used,  
c) type of operating system.  
2) The Website automatically downloads geographic data as well as data on the activities performed by the User, which will be used only for marketing or statistical analyses.  
3) In some Websites, Asseco Data Systems S.A. applies mechanisms for profiling a given Usage within a given Website, namely, it data on the User’s activity is collected, in particular: search history, clicks on a given Website, visits to a given Website and its subpages, dates of logging in and registration of the User in a given Website, data on the use of specific services in a given Website.

### 3\. Use and protection of the User’s personal data by the Website

1) The Controller of the Users’ data listed in section 2(1) of the Privacy Policy is Asseco Data Systems S.A.  
2) In cases defined by special regulations, the User has the right to access the contents of their data, the right to correct it as well as the right to demand its removal from the database.  
3) User data will also be made available to state administration bodies, law enforcement bodies and judicial authorities at their express request and only in the cases specified by generally applicable law.

### 4\. Cookies:

1) When you use the Website, the storage on your device stores DoubleClick Cookies that:  
a) collect information on the use of the content of the Website (they contain a randomly  
generated 18-digit, unique identifier assigned to web browsers installed on specific  
devices of the User),  
b) are used to store the logged in User’s data to a given Website (active sessions)  
concerning, among others, the selected language of the Website, settings of search filters,  
User’s data (login or name) used to log in to a given Website, or the authorization token in  
a given Website.  
2) The device identifier stored in a Double Click cookie file is added to a remarketing list that is  
stored on Google servers and grouped by category.  
3) The information stored in the Cookie files on the User’s device’s storage is then used for  
remarketing purposes.  
4) Remarketing consists in using data collected in Cookie files by external providers in order to  
display advertisements based on data collected during the User’s use of the contents of the  
Website.  
5) The User can deactivate the use of cookies in their web browser by means of the option to turn  
Google ads off or on the Network Advertising Initiative website.  
6) Cookies in no way modify other data stored in the User’s device’s storage, nor do they affect  
the proper operation of the operating system.

### 5\. Newsletter:

1) The User has the possibility to agree to receive the Newsletter. For this purpose, the User  
must provide their data in the field concerning the Newsletter or fill in the appropriate form,  
placed on the Website, in which they provide, among others, the following information:  
a) e-mail address,  
b) name and surname  
2) The User may at any time withdraw their consent to receive the Newsletter by clicking the  
“unsubscribe” button in the Newsletter content or by submitting an appropriate application  
available at the following address [https://www.daneosobowe.assecods.pl](https://www.daneosobowe.assecods.pl/).

### 6\. Final provisions

1) The Website reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. In matters not regulated by the  
law, the relevant provisions of the generally applicable law shall apply.  
2) The following form an integral part of the Privacy Policy:  
a) Appendix No. 1 – List of Websites,  
[https://www.assecods.pl/wp-content/uploads/appendix\_ADS\_privacy\_policy.pdf](https://www.assecods.pl/wp-content/uploads/appendix_ADS_privacy_policy.pdf)  
3) This Privacy Policy shall be effective as of 25 May 2018.

#### Related articles

*  [ The form enabling the submission of a non-qualified certificate revocation request](https://support.certum.eu/en/cert-process-of-revoking-form-en/)
*  [ QSCert®, spol. s r.o. certificates confirming the compliance of Asseco Data Systems Certum (Certum) services with the provisions of the eIDAS Regulation](https://support.certum.eu/en/qscert-certification/)

Was this helpful?

How can we improve it?

The instructions did not lead me to solve the problemThe article is written in a difficult language for meOther

What others?

Send your opinion

Didn’t find the answer to your question?
----------------------------------------

### Ask our consultant

Get advice from our consultants

Electronic signature
--------------------

Certificates
------------

About us
--------

All rights reserved to Asseco Data Systems S.A. - 2022

Manage Cookie Consent

This website uses cookies and other tracking technologies to help navigate and provide feedback, analyze the use of our products and services, support our promotional and marketing efforts, and provide content from third parties.  
  
Check [out more cookies settings](https://www.certum.eu/en/cookie-policy-eu/) to manage your preferences.  
  
More information on cookies and data storage can be found in our [Privacy policy](#)

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept cookies Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent
